ANASTASIIA KIIAS



EDUCATION

06.2023 - 09.2023

UX/UI Designer

Spiced Academy Bootcamp, Berlin

2010 - 2015

MA in Hotel & Restaurant

Business

Zaporizhzhia National University, Ukraine

EXPERTISE

- UI Design
- Prototyping & Wireframing
- Responsive Web Design
- Information Architecture
- User Centered Design
- User Research

SOFTWARE

- FigmaNotion
- FramerMiro

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian English

Native Professional proficiency Proficiency

PRODUCT DESIGNER

anastasiiakiias@amail.com

My LinkedIn

+49 176 6956 3538

My Portfolio

PROFILE

I am a Product designer, with a background in hospitality, which has refined my abilities to anticipate user needs and communicate effectively. I am focused on creating exclusive user experience through research and a deep understanding of user needs.

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER

2024 - PRESENT

OneFootball GmbH. Berlin

- Developed wireframes, mockups, and prototypes to support product design
- Contributed to design systems and ensured consistency across all product interfaces
- Collaborated with teams to align design solutions with user needs and business goals

TRANSITION TO GERMANY

2021 - 2023

Berlin

- Received Professional Scrum Master™ I (PSM I) at Scrum.org
- Completed 7 courses with Creative Practice
 (WebDesign, UX/UI, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator)

BUSINESS CLASS CABIN CREW 2015 – 2021

Emirates Airline, Dubai

 Effectively communicated instructions to passengers and new team members on 355 flights, demonstrating quick thinking and problemsolving skills over 4,778 flying hours to ensure passenger comfort and minimize disruptions